Daddy, you're sure I've
never been to Africa before?
It looks familiar.
You saw the same scenery
last summer driving to Las Vegas.
Sure. Where Daddy lost
all that money at the crap...
Hey!
...table.
Hey, look! A camel.
Of course this isn't really Africa,
honey. It's the French Morocco.
Well, it's northern
Africa.
Still seems
like Las Vegas.
We're just 100 miles
north of the Sahara desert.
Do you realize
that, son?
I don't know. In school, they
call this the dark continent.
This is twice as
bright as Indianapolis.
You just wait till
we get to Marrakech.
Marrakesh?
Sounds like a drink.
It sure does.
Wait a minute.
Hold on here.
What's the matter?
Well, I sure want
to thank you.
Without your help, anything
might have happened here.
My Measure,
monsieur.
There are moments in life
when we all need a little help.
Yeah. Just what
was the trouble?
Your little boy accidentally
pulled off his wife's veil.
You know?
Yeah.
Hank!
I want to introduce
my wife, Mrs. McKenna.
How do you do?
How do you do, madame?
My name is
Louis Bernard.
Well, we thank you
very much, Mr. Bernard.
That's our son, Hank.
Hello, Hank.
Hello.
You talk Arab talk.
A few words.
Why was he so angry?
It was just an accident.
But the Muslim religion
allows for few accidents.
Yeah, I suppose so.
May I...
Yeah, sit down right
in front of Jo there.
I thought
his name was Hank.
No, it's my wife's name.
You see, J—O. No "."E
How different.
It's short
for Josephine.
I've called her that so long nobody
knows her by any other name.
No. Do they?
I do. Mommy.
Yeah.
Forgot about that.
Now, about
the accident.
You see, a Muslim woman
never takes off her veil in public
under any circumstances. I see.
You mean they feed
intravenously?
No, Hank.
What a big word
for such a small boy.
You see,
I'm a doctor.
Well,
he sounds like one.
Yeah.
He can spell hemoglobin.
Of course, he has a little trouble
with words like dog and cat.
Where do you
practice, Doctor?
Indianapolis, Indiana. Good
Samaritan Hospital out there.
What brings you
to Marrakech?
You see, we were attending
a medical convention in Paris.
And I thought as much as
as we were in Europe,
I'd come down and
see Morocco again.
Daddy liberated
Africa.
Well, I was stationed
up in Casablanca
at an army field hospital
during the war.
Do you live in Morocco,
Mr. Bernard?
No.
I suppose you came
directly from Paris.
We looked in on
Lisbon and Rome.
And Casablanca.
I hope you will have time
to truly enjoy Marrakech.
Well, let's see. We'll have
at the most about three days.
You will naturally be stopping at
the hotels La Mamounia or La Menara.
Why do you ask?
Because they are hotels
for tourists of good taste.
Do you live in
France, Mr. Bernard?
Sometimes.
Do you eat snails?
When I'm lucky
enough to get them.
Well, if you ever get hungry, our
garden back home is full of snails.
Thank you for
the invitation.
That's all right. We tried
everything to get rid of them.
We never thought
of a Frenchman.
Here we go.
Say, do you want to share a
taxi with us down to the hotel?
That's kind of you,
Doctor,
but unfortunately, I
have some business first.
I see.
What business are
you in, Mr. Bernard?
However, I'll be there later. Perhaps
we might have a drink together.
Well, no, come up to our
suite. We'll have a drink up there.
In that case, I will
take you to dinner.
No, that's not fair.
But I know Marrakesh.
I can show you an
intriguing Arab restaurant
where the food is different
and the manner of eating exotic.
Well, that's what we came
here for. How about it, Jo?
How about one of
those Arabian nights?
I'd love it.
How would you prefer to travel
to the hotel? By taxi, fiacre?
Gee, I don't know.
A wagon! I wanna
ride in a wagon!
Well, I guess
it's a wagon.
See you later.
Au revoir. I look
forward to the cocktails.
Good-bye. Come on.
Bye.
Hank, you sit up
with the driver.
How do you like this?
A horse-drawn convertible.
Well, I just saw Louis
Bernard talking to that Arab.
What Arab?
The one that was shouting
at Hank for pulling the veil off.
They were talking like
they were very dear friends.
Well, he probably knew him
before. What does that mean?
It means that Mr. Bernard
is a very mysterious man.
What? He seemed
perfectly normal to me.
Now, what do you
really know about him?
What do I know about
him? I know his name.
We were sitting there.
We were talking.
You don't know anything
about this man,
and he knows everything
there is to know about you.
Wait.
He knows that you live
in Indianapolis, Indiana.
He knows that you're a doctor
at the Good Samaritan Hospital.
And he knows that you attended
a medical convention in Paris,
and that you stopped off in
Rome, and Lisbon and Casablanca
for just a few days.
All right.
And he knows that you served in
north Africa in an army field hospital.
Honey, it was just a casual
conversation. That's all.
Darling, you weren't
just talking casually.
He was asking all kinds of questions,
and you were answering them.
You might as well have
handed him your passport.
Well, what's
the difference?
We just have a conversation.
I've got nothing to hide.
I have a feeling
that Mr. Bernard has.
Honey.
I know this is
mysterious Morocco,
but we're not going to
lose our head, are we?
I know.
I know what it is.
What?
Why, you're sore because this
fella didn't ask you any questions.
Hardy-har-har.
Hardy-hat.
Well, this eases
the pain.
What pain, Mommy?
It's just an expression, honey.
Hey, can you take care
of the driver? Yes, sir.
My name is McKenna,
Dr. McKenna.
I'll take care of
everything, sir.
Come on.
We're being watched.
What? Come on!
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
When I was just a little boy
I asked my mother
what will I be
He'll make
a fine doctor.
Will I be handsome?
Will I be rich?
Here's what she said to me
Come on, darling.
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be,
will be
The future's
not ours to see
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
Second verse.
When I was
just a child in school
I asked my teacher
what should I try
Catch.
Should I paint pictures?
Should I sing songs?
This was her wise reply
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be, will
be
The future's not
ours to see
Que sera, sera
Oops!
What will be, will be
May I have this next dance? Yes.
All right.
You're divine.
Dinner for the boy.
Yeah, come in. Right
around the corner.
I can't tell you how
beautifully your wife sings.
Pretty good,
isn't she?
She's marvelous.
Too bad it was
interrupted.
I had that same feeling
myself many times.
Well, everything's fine.
The manager has
a babysitter for us.
Good.
Mrs. McKenna, permit me the
pleasure of serving you a drink.
I would love it.
Thank you.
Were you on the American
stage, Mrs. McKenna?
Yes, Mr. Bernard, I was
on the American stage,
and the London stage,
and the Paris stage.
I thought perhaps you had
seen me in Paris, being French.
You know, the
theater requires time,
and for me, time
is often a luxury.
Have you ever been
to Paris, Mr. Bernard?
I was born there.
What business are you in?
I buy and sell.
What?
Whatever gives
the best profit.
Well, now that
you're in Marrakech,
what are you
buying and selling?
You know, I would much
rather talk about the stage.
If you tell me what
shows you are in...
Would you excuse me?
I'll get it.
No, I got it.
No, IWill.
I'm inquiring for the room
of Monsieur Montgomery.
He asked me for
a drink, and I...
I'm sorry. There's
no Montgomery here.
Pardon me, monsieur.
I regret disturbing you.
Okay.
May I use your
telephone, please?
Yeah, sure.
It's right there.
Mommy!
Yes?
I can't
cut this meat.
IWIdoitforyou,
dean
Hello?
I'm terribly sorry, but I cannot
go to dinner with you tonight.
I have neglected
an important matter
which now requires
my attention.
I see.
Perhaps
another night?
Sure. Sure. We'll
get together again.
Good-bye.
Good night.
Bye.
My name's McKenna.
Of course. The hotel
phoned. Follow me, please.
I think you will
find this comfortable.
Thank you very much.
Honey, move over here.
Let me sit out there.
You're on my dress.
VVhoop!
Yeah.
We always wash the
hands before eating.
Thank you.
VVhoop!
Those people
are staring at us.
What people?
Right in back of us.
What?
Yes.
Here.
They were staring at us
in front of the hotel too.
Jo, will you please
stop imagining things?
I'm not.
Good evening. You must
think me awfully rude.
I've been staring at you ever
since I saw you at the hotel.
You are Jo Conway,
the Jo Conway?
Yes, I am.
Didn't I tell you?
I knew I was right.
I'm Lucy Drayton,
and this is my husband.
How do you do?
We're Dr. and
Mrs. McKenna.
My wife tells me
Mrs. McKenna appeared
at the London Palladium
a few years ago.
Of course, we hardly
ever see a show now.
Edward is such an
old stick in the mud.
So I have to console
myself with your records.
I must admit I love them.
I'm not one for
this terrible bebop
or whatever you
call it.
Thank you very much. When
are you coming back to London?
Possibly never again,
professionally.
Don't say you're
giving up the stage.
Well, temporarily,
I am.
Well, it's just
that I'm a doctor,
and you know, a doctor's
wife never has as much time...
What my husband
is trying to say
is Broadway musical shows are
not produced in Indianapolis, Indiana.
Well, you know... Of course,
we could live in New York.
I hear that doctors aren't
starving there either.
Well, it's not that I have any
objection to working in New York.
It's just that it'd be
hard for my patients
to come from
Indianapolis for treatment.
You know, dear, I'm always
saying the wrong thing. I'm sorry.
Not in the least.
Tell me,
Dr. McKenna, do you also go...
Hey, why don't all of you sort of
turn around here or something.
It's kind of kind
of hard on the neck.
It's in one of
our English counties.
It's not what
you'd call a farm.
It's really more
of a small holding.
Here we are.
Isn't that
fascinating?
Yes.
There we are.
Hey, they look good.
Surprise.
They look wonderful.
Looks like bread.
We're not going to
eat all that, are we?
No.
Is that the way you
do it? Just break it?
Yes, just break it. Just
break it. Just like this.
It won't break.
No.
Well, I'm gonna...
There.
Is that the way
you do it?
That's quite all right.
That was
a tough one.
Does it chew any
better than it tears?
Is it fattening?
I imagine
it might be.
No, it's pretty
good,hon.
Well, I...
No plate.
No?
No.
No knife or forks.
That's right. I understand
you're just supposed to dig in.
Allow me to show you,
will you?
You use only the first two
fingers and thumb of the right hand.
You don't use the
other two fingers,
and always the left
hand in the lap.
I see.
May I show you?
Just these two
fingers?
Can I help you?
I'll hold it for you.
That's it.
There we are.
Well...
Boy, could I use this
hand now. I can't...
It's all right. Nobody
minds. No one minds.
That's good style.
No one minds.
It's messy,
but worth it.
I think I'll practice
on an olive.
Honey, it's wonderful.
Here. Take a bite.
Good?
Yeah.
Tell me, does this
way of eating
have to do with
religion or something?
I think it's more
social than religious.
I don't know.
It seems like to me if you have
four good fingers and a thumb,
you ought to be able
to use all of them.
It's very good,
isn't it?
Very good.
Well, as I was saying,
I was quite happy farming my bit
of land down in Buckinghamshire
when these United Nations
fellows started worrying me.
Edward was a big noise
in the Ministry of Food
during the war,
you know.
So we pulled ourselves
up by the roots,
and here we are,
United Nations Relief.
Sounds like
interesting work.
I'm preparing a report on
soil erosion at the moment.
You know,
parts of this country
are not unlike your
Dust Bowl formation.
A thin layer of topsoil
and underneath...
How do you like that? First he
promises to take us to dinner...
Yeah. Well, we just
met him today, honey.
You can't expect him
to change his whole life.
Ben, what's the
matter with you?
What's the matter
with me?
There's nothing the matter with
me. What's the matter with you?
I just don't want to
be insulted. That's all.
You're not
being insulted.
After all, you can't
blame him, can we,
for turning down an old married
couple like us for a girl like that.
We're not an old
married couple!
All right.
All right, he's a heel.
I don't understand him,
but I'm beginning not to like
what he's doing to our whole night.
I must do
some shopping in the market tomorrow.
I do hope it'll be fine.
Well, not too fine.
Of course, I know that our
English weather is pretty awful,
but sometimes, you know, I think
we don't realize when we're lucky.
All this sunshine
day after day,
well, it doesn't
seem natural somehow.
I want to get up.
Ben, don't.
I know you. Once you get
worked up, you start a fight.
Now, forget about him.
Will you come to the
market with us tomorrow?
As a matter of fact, Louis
Bernard, the big buyer from Paris,
was going to take us to
the marketplace tomorrow.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I'll
go over and cancel out.
Now, Ben, sit down and eat
your dinner. It's getting cold.
We'd love to go.
Good, good.
We'd be delighted.
I don't know why he gets so
worked up over unimportant things.
Monsieur!
What's he saying,
Mrs. Drayton?
He's the teller
of tales, Hank.
Isn't this exciting?
Just like the county
fair when I was a kid.
They got everything but
the balloon ascension.
What's so funny about that? Did
you ever see a balloon ascension?
No, you know what
I was just thinking?
You know what's paying for
these three days in Marrakech?
Me.
Mrs. Campbell's
gallstones.
You know the purse I
bought in Paris? Yeah.
Bill Edward's tonsils.
Mommy! Daddy!
Daddy, come with us! We're
gonna see the medicine man.
Maybe you can learn
something, Daddy.
I wouldn't be
a bit surprised.
Anytime he starts
wearing you out...
I haven't enjoyed
the market so much.
You know, I never
thought of it that way before.
What?
I'm wearing Johnny
Matthews' appendix.
Dear.
What about the boat trip?
Let's see, it took
two boys, one girl
and two sets of twins,
didn't it?
And Mrs. Morgan's
hives.
Well, how are the
acrobats today?
Wonderful.
Watch that kid that goes clear
to the top there. He's great.
I'll see you later.
Yes.
All the way home, we'll be
riding on Herbie Taylor's ulcers.
And AIIida Markle's
asthma.
Now, if we could
just get four cases
of the seven-year itch,
we could retire.
Or if Mrs. Yarro's really
gonna have triplets,
we could completely redecorate
the house, couldn't we?
What would they say
if they heard us?
You know, one of the reasons I
came to a place like Marrakech
is so we could say things like
that Without everybody hearing us.
Well, I'd like to say something
where nobody could hear us.
This is
the safest place.
When are we going
to have another baby?
You're the doctor.
You have all the answers.
Yeah, but this is the first time
I've ever heard the question.
Mommy, look!
Come here!
Look. Sewing machines. Looks
like a television commercial.
Having a good time,
Hank?
I guess so.
He's delighted
with everything.
Coming through! Coming through!
Hank! Hank,
come back here!
Hank!
It's best to keep
out of trouble, Hank.
What's going on?
Looks like the police
are chasing somebody.
Hey.
Hey, look there.
You better stand back.
Go on. Stand back.
Monsieur McKenna.
I'm Louis Bernard.
A man, a statesman,
he is to be killed,
assassinated, in London.
Soon, very soon.
Tell them in London.
Ambrose Chappell.
Ben, who is he?
Louis Bernard.
You got something to
write on? Louis Bernard?
He's dead.
He says,
"Do you know this man?"
Yes, we do know him.
He's Louis Bernard, the...
Louis Bernard?
Monsieur and
Madame McKenna.
He wants you to go to police
headquarters to make a statement.
Okay.
Our friends have to go
to the police station.
I think I better go with
them. Yes, of course.
You don't want your little boy to
go, do you?
But I
want to go to the police station.
I think it better if I take him
back to the hotel, don't you?
Would you please?
Certainly.
Thank you.
You be a good boy, Hank.
We're to be going now.
Heaven knows when
we shall be back.
Ben, why do you suppose
he turned up in an Arab outfit
and wearing make-up?
What's more important,
why was he killed?
I'll bet he was a spy
or something like that.
What were you writing down?
What was he telling you?
I'll tell you later.
What is it?
I just feel
kind of funny.
Why should he pick
me out to tell?
After what we said about
him last night, the poor fella.
When we get in
with the inspector,
I'll do my best to cut
some of the red tape.
Fine. Fine.
Well, I'm going
to stretch a bit.
I'm afraid the questions
will go on till doomsday
if you admit you knew
this chap Bernard before.
I don't know him at all.
We met yesterday on a bus.
They're a cynical lot,
you know, these French.
They might refuse
to believe that.
Well, they've got to
believe it. It's the truth.
Look at it from
their point of view.
They saw this poor
fellow whispering to you,
and then they saw you
write something down.
Are you gonna show
them what you wrote?
Thank you, Mr. Drayton, but a
translator will not be necessary.
Won't you come inside,
madame, monsieur?
Please do me
the kindness to wait.
I might have questions
for you later.
Very good.
Passports, please.
You came to French
Morocco four days ago.
That's right.
You are a doctor, sir?
Yes, I'm a surgeon, a
tourist and American citizen.
Three good reasons
why you should have
nothing in common
with Louis Bernard.
I didn't have.
You were in Paris
recently?
Yes, I was attending
a medical convention.
You came to Marrakech
with him in the same bus,
had an aperitif with
him in your hotel room,
and you ate at the same
restaurant last night.
Yes, but at
different tables.
So Louis Bernard is
a stranger to you?
I met him for the first time
in my life yesterday on a bus.
And yet out of 5,000 people
in a great marketplace,
he comes to you when
he is about to die.
Is that the action of a casual
acquaintance, monsieur?
I know absolutely nothing
about Louis Bernard.
No. Not even, I suppose, that he
was an agent of the Deuxieme Bureau?
What's that?
Perhaps you have also never
heard of the American FBI?
Now, wait...
It would be so much easier
for both of us, monsieur,
if you would
cease to pretend.
Look here...
The dead man found out what
he had been sent here to discover.
That's why he was killed.
He told you what he
had discovered. Why?
Because he placed complete
confidence in you. Not true?
Boy, you not only
ask the questions,
you answer them too,
don't you?
Let me ask you a question.
Assuming that Bernard trusted
me as implicitly as you say,
then I'd never reveal anything
he said to me, would I?
Even Americans, I suppose,
find it sometimes desirable
to betray a confidence.
Wait a minute. Let's get
some things straight here.
I'm a tourist. I'm
traveling for pleasure.
I somehow got involved in
this very unfortunate incident.
I came here to make a
simple statement of fact
and not be subjected
to a police grilling.
Monsieur,
I would like you...
No, you let me finish. Now, let
me finish.
Entrez!
Wait a minute.
Did he say I was
wanted on the telephone?
I'll take that call now.
And you just take it easy.
Hello.
Dr. McKenna?
This is Dr. McKenna.
Who's this?
If you tell even one word
of what Louis Bernard whispered
to you in the marketplace,
your little boy will
be in serious danger.
Remember, say nothing.
Hello?
Drayton?
Didn't you tell me your
wife was going to take Hank
right straight back
to the hotel?
I thought so, yes.
Well, call her up.
Somebody just called me
and threatened me about Hank.
Go on. Call her up.
See if he's all right.
Hotel Mamounia?
My wife doesn't answer.
Concierge?
What's your room number?
Four fourteen.
I can't believe it.
She hasn't come
back yet?
At least nobody's
seen her.
All right, now you
go back to the hotel.
And see if you can
find out What's going on.
It's so unlike my wife.
I'll take care of the police
and join you as soon as I can.
Look here. Don't worry. It's probably
some stupid misunderstanding.
If I find anything out before you
get back, I'll telephone you here.
Just don't waste
any time.
Good-bye.
Who was it, Ben?
It was the concierge
at the hotel.
He found out we were
being held by the police.
He just called up to see if
there was anything he could do.
That's very nice of him.
Yes, I thought so.
I told him if we weren't
back there in 15 minutes,
for him to call the American
Consulate at Casablanca.
But, monsieur, if you had
only told me in the first place
that you wished to
consult with yourconsuL
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, Jo.
There is just one
small formality.
I must request you to sign
a statement of the facts.
If it doesn't take
too long, of course.
But a moment.
I will send for a typist.
Ben?
Yeah?
Ben, aren't you going to
let me see the message?
I don't...
I don't think
I should.
Darling, I'm not
the police inspector.
I'm your wife, and I
think that I should see it.
Ben, why didn't you
give this to the police?
Because I didn't want to.
But, Ben,
a man's life...
Is at stake.
Yeah, I know.
I just... I don't know
what's the right thing to do.
Look, I think we should
go back to the hotel,
pick up Hank, and get out
of here as quickly as we can.
Maybe.
Darling,
think about Hank.
What a terrible thing
this is for him,
seeing a man murdered
right before his eyes.
It's a horrible shock
to a little boy.
I know.
Why don't you take that note,
give it to the American Consulate?
And let's not get any
more involved, please.
Why don't you get the key?
I'll take care of the driver.
All right.
Say, you know
a Mrs. Drayton?
English lady.
That's right.
Did you see her coming
from the marketplace
any time in
the last hour or so?
No, sir.
Now, wait a minute. You
understand this is very important.
She had a little boy
with her, my little boy.
No, sir.
Well, what about
Mr. Drayton?
Mr. Drayton checked out.
He what?
Checked out.
But he couldn't have.
Yes, sir, he did.
No, Mr. Drayton, the Englishman
with the horn-rimmed glasses.
Yes, sir.
He checked out.
I don't know
about you, but I'm exhausted.
IguesslWIcaH
Mrs. Drayton.
Tell her we're back.
She can bring up Hank.
Just hold that
call a minute, Jo.
Why?
Because I asked you to!
Ben, are we about to
have our monthly fight?
I hope not.
Well, then stop
acting like that.
I merely said I was
going to call Mrs. Drayton.
Just a minute.
Wait a minute.
I want you to take
these. They'll relax you.
Relax me?
I'm so relaxed I'm tired.
I think maybe
you need them.
These are for you, Jo.
Now, come on.
I'm the doctor.
Here.
Ben.
Jo, you know what happens
when you get excited and nervous.
Now, here.
Do me a favor.
Six months ago, you told
me I took too many pills.
Six months ago, you
weren't a witness to a murder.
Now, you've been excited.
You've been talking a blue streak.
You've been walking
around in circles.
Ihaven%!
Jo, I make my living knowing when
and how to administer medicine.
Now I know you'll feel better if you
take these. Why fight me on this?
All right, you don't
think you will feel better.
I'll make a deal
with you.
We'll make a deal.
What is this?
Well, there's something
about this Louis Bernard,
and the police station,
and this whole spy business
I haven't told you yet.
What?
Here's the price of
curiosity. What is it?
Come on. Come on.
There's one way of finding out.
All right, Dr. McKenna. I'm
now relaxed and listening.
Well, there's been something
strange about this whole thing
from the very beginning.
Now it wasn't any accident
that Louis Bernard came up to us,
and helped us on the bus,
and started up a conversation.
You were right about him.
You see there?
I know. I know.
That's what I said.
You were right about him.
He was strange.
Yes, I know all that. But
what were you going to tell me?
He started to talk to us, and
the reason he started to talk to us
was 'cause he was
on the lookout
for a suspicious
married couple.
There's nothing very
suspicious-looking about us, is there?
No, because he was wrong. It
was a different married couple.
And he was killed
before he found them?
No, he found them.
He found them, all right.
It was in the restaurant
where we had dinner last night.
And that's one of the
reasons he was killed.
You'll be telling me next
it's Mr. and Mrs. Drayton.
That's who it was, Jo.
Ben, if this is your idea of a
joke, it's not a very funny one.
I think I'll lie down.
Now, listen to me.
Jo.
Now, listen to me
very carefully.
That phone call at
the police station,
that wasn't the concierge
at the hotel.
That was a man with a
foreign voice, and he told me
if I mentioned one
single word of What
Louis Bernard told me
in the marketplace,
that something
would happen to Hank.
Hank? Why Hank?
They've taken him away.
But Mrs. Drayton brought
him back to the hotel.
Mrs. Drayton never got back to
the hotel, and neither did Hank.
But Mr. Drayton...
Listen, Jo.
Mr. Drayton checked out
of the hotel 40 minutes ago.
Now, come on, Jo.
Now, sit down.
I could kill you! You gave
me sedatives!
Jo, sit down.
You did! Let go!
Why didn't you tell me?
I wasn't sure
until now.
You did! You did!
Jo, please! Please!
Let go of me! Let go!
Ben!
Lie down, Jo.
Ben, let me find my baby!
Please.
Dear God!
I want my boy!
Jo, please.
Please! Please.
Where is he, Ben? Jo.
Forgive me, Jo.
Forgive me.
There's still no
word of him, Jo.
The Draytons are
definitely gone.
The register in the hotel
says they came from London.
Drayton told the concierge
he was a college professor.
I don't think there's
anything we can do here, Jo.
I can't bring the
police in on this thing.
I'd even thought of
taking that chance.
But the minute they connect
Hank's disappearance
with Louis Bernard's
murder,
then the first
thing they'll do
is make me tell them
what Louis Bernard
whispered to me
in the marketplace.
That won't do
Hank any good.
I'm going to London.
The Draytons had a private
airplane. I found that out.
That's how they
got Hank out of here.
It could land anyplace. No
trouble with passports or anything.
So we're going to
London to find him.
Jo, now listen to me.
This is what Bernard said.
"A man, a statesman, is
to be killed, assassinated,
"in London.
Soon, very soon.
"Tell them in London
to try Ambrose Chappell."
That's the fella
we've got to find.
And if he knows
anything about this,
I'm gonna offer him every
penny I have to get Hank back.
The Chappell guy's our only
hope. You understand that, Jo?
Now, I've got a car
waiting downstairs.
I've paid the hotel bill. We
get packed, we'll be all set.
Honey?
We don't have much time. You'll
have to get up and start getting ready.
Please, Jo.
Would you just wait, sir,
for the press photographers?
Will you come
this way, madam?
Jo, darling,
love from the fan club!
How could they
remember me so well, Ben?
It's been four years
since I played London.
You're the kind of gal
they don't forget.
Who told them we were
coming? Ben, you didn't.
All I did was wire your friends,
the Parnells, to get us hotel rooms.
I never figured on
anything like this.
Dr. and Mrs. McKenna,
I'm Inspector Edington of the
Criminal Investigation Department.
As things are, there's no need
for you to go through the Customs.
Come this way.
How about
a photo, Jo?
Hi, Jo!
This way, please.
We want Jo!
We want Jo! We want Jo! We want Jo!
We want Jo! We want Jo!
This is Mr. Woburn.
Dr. and Mrs. McKenna.
How do you do?
What do you people
want with us?
Mr. Buchanan would like to
have a chat with you inside.
Who's Mr. Buchanan?
Special Branch,
Scotland Yard.
This is Mr. Buchanan.
Dr. and Mrs. McKenna.
How do you do?
Thank you, Woburn.
Do sit down,
won't you?
Let me say at once
that we're shocked
that your son was taken
from you in Marrakech,
and deeply sympathetic.
Do you know
where he is?
Have you heard anything
about our boy?
I only wish I could give
you some cheerful news,
but we might find him quite
soon indeed if we work together.
Bernard the Frenchman was
sent to Morocco at our request
to check up on an
assassination plot here in London.
You know, a good agent
keeps on staking his life.
He doesn't always win.
Bernard reckoned you
were a man to trust.
He relied on you
to come to us.
Those people kidnapped your
boy in order to keep your mouth shut.
That's right, isn't it?
No, I think they
took him for money.
Then why didn't you go straight
to your consulate in Casablanca?
Why did you come
to London?
Well, I...
Mr. Buchanan...
No, no.
You're convinced that these
people brought your son to London.
You're convinced that you
can find him off your own bat.
You can't.
It's impossible.
But with the help we can
give you, there's a chance,
a really good chance.
But they told us
not to say anything.
Anything you tell me will be in
the most absolute confidence.
Yes, that may
be true, but...
Your son is the trump
card these people hold.
He's perfectly safe
for the moment.
And when they've
done what they want,
they'll let him go.
Is that the idea?
Are we supposed to
just sit here and wait?
No, Mrs. McKenna.
If they consider your boy a
nuisance afterwards, I'm afraid...
There's no need for you to
try and scare us, Mr. Buchanan.
That's exactly what I am
trying to do, scare you.
I'm trying to prevent a man
being murdered here in London.
If you don't tell
me all you know,
you become an accessory
before the fact of murder.
Ben, what can we
do by ourselves?
Now, wait a minute.
Now, wait just a minute.
You've been working
on the wrong McKenna.
Louis Bernard talked to me. He
didn't talk to my Wife, you know.
Then you tell me.
He was a Frenchman.
He spoke to me in French,
and I don't understand a
single word of the language!
Ben, maybe they could
find those people and Hank.
Maybe. Maybe's not
good enough for me.
And I don't think it ought to
be good enough for you either.
You act as if you're the only
one who's concerned about...
Honey, honey, I
didn't mean it that way.
We made up our minds what
we're gonna do about this thing.
Now let's try
and stick to it.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Buchanan,
we'd like to cooperate with you
on this thing, but we just can't.
Well,
I've got a son of my own.
I don't know What I'd do.
Excuse me.
Telephone call for you,
Mrs. McKenna.
Put the telephone call for Mrs.
McKenna through here, please.
Hello.
Mrs. McKenna?
Yes?
This is Mrs. Drayton.
Do you remember me?
Mrs. Drayton.
Where is our son?
Where have you got him?
He's here with me. You
mustn't worry about him, really.
Where's our son?
Where have you got him?
I expect you'd like to
speak to him, wouldn't you?
Yes, please! Please.
Hank! Hello, Hank!
Just a minute.
Mommy?
Mommy, is that you?
Hank, darling,
are you really all right?
I'm a little scared, Mommy,
but I'm all right, I guess.
I miss you, Mommy.
I miss you so much!
Here. Hank. Hank, this
is Daddy.
Is Mommy crying?
Now, Hank, listen to me.
Where are you?
I didn't mean to
make her cry, Daddy,
but I'm scared,
and I want to see her.
Hank, son, now listen. Tell me
where you are. Where are you?
Welbeck eight...
Yeah?
Eight. Go on, Hank.
Hank!
Ben, he was so scared.
It was a London
telephone exchange.
Public call box.
West One.
Do I have to say any
more? Come on, dear.
You may change
your minds.
If you do,
this number
will find me.
Baggage and
airport service for 552 from Paris...
Everything all right,
sir? Yeah, yeah.
Your room key, sir.
Thank you.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
There you are.
It's from the Parnells.
"Welcome home, Jo.
"Look forward to seeing your
family, especially the little one."
"With love, from Jan and
Cindy." That's very nice.
"Ambrose Chappell."
There he is, big as life.
"61 Burdett Street, Camden
Town. Gulliver 6198."
What are you
going to say?
I'm gonna tell him
I'll keep my mouth shut
and offer him all the
money we have for Hank.
Operator?
Operator,
I want Gulliver 6198.
|'|| get it.
Jo! You look wonderful!
Jo!
When we got your Wire,
I couldn't believe it.
What were you doing
down in Morocco?
Sightseeing.
You're the perfect answer
to what London needs, Jo.
This week's the dullest
thing since my first show.
Ambrose Chappell.
Mr. Ambrose Chappell.
Mr. Conway, I didn't
know you were there.
Dr. McKenna. Dr. McKenna.
Welcome to London town, Doctor.
I am sorry. I knew you were
married. But a doctor? How clever.
Especially in such
a psychosomatic business.
Jan, will you
keep quiet?
Honey, you wouldn't know
what psychosomatic means.
I do too. It means when your
mind gets sick of your body,
it does something to it.
Can't you see the
doctor's trying to telephone?
Not at all. It's just some
business. It's nothing.
Business is everything.
Shh!
Hello. Hello?
Ambrose Chappell.
I say, is this
Mr. Ambrose Chappell?
Well, my name's McKenna.
Dr. Benjamin McKenna.
I don't think we need to be
quiet. Would you like a drink?
I was wondering if you'd be at
your address for a little while.
I'd like to speak to
you for a few minutes.
Yes. Thank you.
I'll be right over.
I'd like all of you
to meet my husband.
I've heard so much
about you, Doctor.
It's nice to
see you in person.
How do you do, sir?
This is Val's wife, Helen.
How do you do?
You look just
like those pictures
Jo had in her dressing
room four years ago.
Haven't changed a bit.
Why should he?
He's a doctor.
Probably gets
free hormones.
Yes.
I'm Jan Peterson. I sing
almost as well as your wife.
And, darling, this is Cindy
Fontaine from Harrisburg, PA.
Harrisburg.
Been back home lately?
How can I? They know
me there as Elva McDuff.
It doesn't quite fit me
anymore.
Where's your boy? I'd like to
see which one of you he looks like.
He's staying with
some other people
so we could have a
little time by ourselves.
What's his name?
Hank.
Henry, really.
Well, I hope he looks
like you and has the doctor's brain.
These flowers are really so
lovely. We thank you very much.
Well, I'll order
some drinks.
Okay, but dinner
tonight's on me,
a sort of welcome
home for Jo.
I wish I could persuade
her to stay a month.
I wish I could,
Val, but I can't.
I'm terribly sorry, but I have
an appointment I have to keep.
I wonder if you'd order
the drinks, Mr. Parnell.
I'll be back as soon as I
can. Excuse me, please.
Ben, please.
It's got to be done.
Take me with you.
No, no, no. I can't.
I won't disappear.
For the last time,
please let me go with you.
Honey, two people are
easier to follow than one.
Now we don't want
Buchanan's men on our tracks,
the other people either.
I'm going out through
the service entrance.
Yes, sir?
Ambrose Chappell?
Come in.
There's a gent
to see you, sir.
Good afternoon, sir. I am Ambrose
Chappell. What can I do for you?
Well, I...
If you gave me your name,
that might be a start.
Yes, of course. My name is
McKenna. Dr. Benjamin McKenna.
I phoned you.
Yes, yes.
You are Ambrose Chappell?
Well, I've been Ambrose
Chappell for nearly 71 years.
But I think I understand
your problem.
You do?
Certainly.
It happens all the time.
You expected
someone else.
Just a moment.
Ambrose?
I think this gentleman
wants to talk to us.
Now, Father, why don't
you go and have a nice rest?
I have centuries of rest
ahead of me, thank you.
Good day to you, sir.
Now, what can
I do for you?
I'm Dr. McKenna.
That name mean
anything to you?
No. No, I don't think so.
You've no idea
why I'm here?
My dear sir,
Ihaven%the faintest idea.
But your name
was given to me
by someone I happened
to meet in Marrakech.
Yes?
Yes.
Now, I think you know this man,
Louis Bernard, a Frenchman.
Louis Bernard?
Come on. Let's stop
fooling around.
Bernard told me to come
here just before he died.
This man is dead?
You know he's dead
just as well as I do.
Now, I've come here with
a business proposition.
I don't see how you
can turn it down.
Exactly What
had you in mind?
You want to talk here?
Certainly.
We have no secrets
from our employees.
Okay. Now,
in the first place,
I haven't uttered one word of
what Bernard told me before he died,
and I never will.
Frankly, I'm not interested
in political intrigue.
I don't care who you fellows
are gonna kill here in London.
All I want is that boy,
and I'll take the next
airplane back to America.
Come on, please.
Listen to me, will you?
Honestly, if money means
anything to you, I'll do...
Father,
call the police quick.
Now, sir, I shall we go into
this a little more carefully...
Wait just a minute.
You told him to call the
police. No, no. No, no.
What's the idea,
trying to bluff me?
My dear sir,
there can be no...
Let me go.
Are you sure you don't
know Louis Bernard?
I've never
heard of him.
You've got no idea
what happened yesterday
in Marrakech or
where my boy is?
Of course not.
Where is he?
William! Edgar!
Davis! Help!
Now, wait a minute! Wait! All
right, now, hold on. Wait. Listen.
It's obvious I'm
in the wrong place.
Now, all right, let
go of me. Come on.
Come on. Listen.
Wait.
Come on.
I made a mistake.
Now let me go.
Hold him! Hold him!
The police are coming.
Hold him.
He said that no matter how
Bud Flanagan was got up,
even if he was
dressed by Hartnell,
that nobody would ever
believe that he was an aristocrat.
So I said,
"Listen, Chris,
"why don't you take William
Hickey's column out of the paper?"
Jo? Jo, what's become of that
unpredictable husband of yours?
He's been gone
over an hour now.
He went to see some man.
What was it? Church?
No. No, it was Chappell.
It's not a man.
It's a place.
It's Ambrose Chapel!
Val, do they list
chapels in the directory?
Let's take a look.
Please help me find it.
Let's see. Here we are.
Ambrose. Here we have a chap...
Ambrose Chapel,
17 Ambrose Street West Two.
17 Ambrose Street,
West Two.
17 Ambrose Street.
Look, darlings, I have
to go. I'm very sorry.
Have another drink, and
I'll be back as soon as I can.
And explain to Ben when
he comes in, would you?
Explain what?
Look, there's something
weird going on here,
and I can't
quite follow it.
Let's try to figure
the whole thing out.
First of all, there
was a man named...
Ambrose Chappell.
And Ben dashed
off to see him.
Then Jo said it wasn't a man
but a place, and she dashed off.
Don't mention it again,
darling, or I might dash off.
Ooh! What a temptation.
Can you fathom it, though?
It's probably some
new American gag.
I'll have to ask
Danny about it.
Well, hello again.
I'm awfully sorry
I had to rush off,
but it was something
that had to be done.
Boy,
I can use this.
Thank you.
Well, I...
Where's Jo? She's
gone to Ambrose Chapel.
I just came
from there.
Hey, not your
Ambrose Chappell.
It isn't a he. It's
an it, a building.
She just left
20 minutes ago.
She... What?
What do you mean?
Where's the address?
I'll look it up again.
What is this? You
say it's a building?
Yes, here it is.
Ambrose Chapel,
17 Ambrose Street,
Bayswater.
Yes? Doctor! Doctor,
come back! It's Jo.
Jo?
Ben?
What happened?
Did you find anything?
No, it was
a wild goose chase.
Darling, it must be
the chapel. I've found it.
It's just
a short way from here.
I know it was crazy
thing to do, but...
Honey, I know the address.
You wait there. I'll be right over.
All right,
I'll meet you outside.
Bye, dear.
What did you say
that address was again?
17 Ambrose Street,
Bayswater.
I don't know
how to thank you.
Three men. You don't know
much about checkers, do you?
You'd better go to bed, dear,
or you'll be overtired.
Can I finish?
I'm winning.
Yes, finish.
Edna, see he has
some milk and biscuits.
He'd better be put to sleep again,
honey. I've got to get downstairs.
No, it's not necessary
tonight.
You'll sleep, Hank,
won't you?
I guess so.
Hurry up if you want
to finish this game.
Look, it doesn't hurt
to be kind, does it?
Give me a yell when you
want me to unlock the door.
- Can I come in?
- Yes.
I wish it was
tomorrow.
That's not a very
orthodox sentiment.
Before I forget.
Here you are,
my friend.
Two tickets for the concert at the
Albert Hall with my compliments.
Your box is
nicely placed.
Or should we say,
strategically placed.
And now, for the
most important part.
What is it?
A record of
the delightful piece
they're going to
play this evening.
Music's less in your
line than marksmanship.
If you listen,
I'm going to play you
the exact moment at
which you can shoot.
So listen carefully.
We'll have it once more. Listen
for the crash of the cymbals.
You see?
At such a moment,
your shot will
never be heard.
Even the listeners
will be undisturbed.
I think the composer would've
appreciated that, don't you?
No one will know.
No one except one.
That's right. If you're
clever, my friend.
Now, any questions,
musical or otherwise?
No.
There's one
comforting thought.
It happens early
in the evening.
And I hope
I shan't upset you
if I tell you you've
only time for one shot.
If you need another,
the risk is yours.
I don't take risks.
I'm very glad
to hear that.
Traipsing all the way
to Marrakech for you,
I should like you
to do me credit.
Your distinguished target
is already on his way.
There's a car waiting for you
downstairs in the back entrance.
You're to pick up
a Miss Benson on the way.
She'll be your
companion in the box.
She'll lend you an air of
respectability if that's possible.
Will you have
the money when I return?
Don't you trust me?
What is your
English proverb?
"A wolf in
sheep's clothing."
A very clever disguise,
I must say.
I think you'd better be going. It's
impolite to be late for a concert.
And it would be awkward if they made
you wait until the first item was over.
Will you show our friend
down to the car, my dear?
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry you have to
sneak out by the back way,
but we must preserve
a respectable front.
There it is.
Yeah. You just may have
hit it right on the nose.
And you can't be farther wrong
than I was with my Ambrose Chappell.
Come on, let's go.
Ben, should we get
some help from the police?
No, honey, please. Let's take
a crack at this alone. Come on.
Ben.
Shh, shh.
This is just
another wild goose chase
Let's wait
And look around
Look who's coming
down the aisle
The subject of my address to
you this evening is adversity.
The average life,
yours and mine,
is often harassed
and perplexed
by disappointments and by
cruelties beyond our control.
Now, strangely enough, it is often
these things beyond our control...
That's
Buchanan's phone number.
You go out, call him up, tell him
to surround this place with police.
What if he asks...
Tell him anything.
This is the time. I'm sure
Hank's around here someplace.
But I don't want to
leave you. I know. I know.
I don't know how else to
do it, honey. You go on now.
...and therefore the
goodness of all mankind.
Few of us pause to consider how
life's adversities work in our behalf
to make better
men and women of us.
But I think we should
pause, and pause now,
to do a little
stocktaking,
to look into our own hearts and
lives and see what we find there.
Therefore, instead of
continuing the service,
I think we should all return to
our homes for private meditation,
remembering how little
we have to complain of
and how much to
be grateful for.
Next week, I shall discuss
the fruits of our meditations.
Until then, my blessing upon
each and every one of you.
Well, this is a pleasant
surprise, Doctor.
Where's my boy,
Drayton?
He's upstairs.
As a matter of fact, you've come just
in time to help my wife with his food.
It seems Hank doesn't care
very much for our English cooking.
What do you want?
I'll give you money. I'll keep my
mouth shut. All I want is my boy.
And what about
your wife?
Did she go outside just
to get a breath of fresh air?
Come on. Tell me what
you want. I'll do anything.
All right, you'll see
your boy all in good time.
Hank! Hank McKenna!
Daddy?
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
I'm here, Daddy! I'm here!
My husband's in there now watching
them. He sent me out to call you
so that you could do something
before they get away.
I'm afraid it isn't quite
as easy as all that.
Mr. Woburn,
my husband is in that chapel
waiting for me to
bring help. Now you...
May I speak to
Mr. Buchanan?
He told me to call him if I needed
him, and I need him right now.
I'm awfully sorry. But I simply
can't get in touch with him just now.
He's gone to a rather important
diplomatic affair at the Albert Hall.
Well, then call him there!
Please call him.
He's on his way.
I don't know quite how...
Mr. Woburn, it isn't a matter
of days. It's a matter of minutes.
Now, you've got
to send some...
You've got to send
the police right away!
Or do I have to go
to Albert Hall myself?
That won't be necessary.
I'll have the chapel put
under immediate observation.
By the time you get back,
a police car should be there.
Please return
to your husband.
Tell him to come straight out of the
chapel and let the police take over.
Woburn, Special Branch.
Hold on.
I must ring off now,
Mrs. McKenna.
Please believe me. I'll
have everything laid on.
There's nobody there.
Are you Mrs. McKenna?
Yes, but there's
something wrong, Officer.
That place was full of
people just a few minutes ago,
and now there's nobody.
Our orders are to keep
it under observation
until the Scotland
Yard car arrives.
But my husband is in there.
There were 30 or 40 people...
When was this?
It was no more
than five minutes ago.
Let's take a look.
I've tried the door.
It's locked.
We'll have to
force it open.
I'm sorry, madam.
We can't break in.
Requires a search warrant.
It's the law, you see.
Well, can't we get one?
That all takes time.
We'll have a look
around, shall we?
Matthews,
take the other end.
All right.
There's no one there.
Are you quite certain this
place was full of people
only a few minutes ago?
Of course I'm certain. I was there
myself sitting next to my husband.
He sent me out to
call Scotland Yard.
Look, I'm afraid it's much
too complicated to explain why.
We'll just have to sit tight and wait
for the car to arrive from the Yard.
As far as we can make out,
there's no sign of life.
Report back here.
I see.
Very good, sir.
Walden, you stand by till
the car arrives from the Yard.
That's all, Matthews.
You're not leaving?
Orders, madam. Can we
give you a lift somewhere?
Yes, take me to
Albert Hall, please.
I'm afraid the Albert
Hall's a little bit off our beat.
Suppose we drop you
at the nearest taxi rank?
All right.
Wait here.
They're here.
Wait till I clear
the kitchen.
Everybody out! Come on. Into
the corridor. Five minutes only!
Come on!
Do as he tells you. Come
on. It'll only take a minute.
Come on. All of you out.
Why? Why?
All right. This way.
Always something funny
going on at this embassy.
Bringing people
in secret.
Give me the Swiss
embassy anytime.
There's neutrality
for you.
Please, may I
see the manager?
I'm sorry, madam. The
manager's on duty in the lobby.
So is his assistant.
I must speak
with one of them.
Which are they?
Over there somewhere.
You have a very nice
little boy, madame.
His safety will depend
upon you tonight.
Where is he?
Good evening.
Is that the
Prime Minister?
No, that's only
the Ambassador.
His Prime Minister's the
one with the bald head.
Your ticket, madam?
I'm sorry.
I'm looking for someone.
I saw the gun. He was
pointing it at the Prime Minister.
He was going to kill him, and
I realized that I had to scream.
Well, then he
didn't kill him?
Your wife saved him. It's
only a small flesh wound.
There they are.
Do please come over
and let the Prime Minister
thank you personally, would you?
I'm sure he'd like to.
It won't take very long.
Would you come along
with me? Don't be nervous.
Prime Minister,
this is the young lady.
Dear lady, I'm
forever in your debt.
This is her
husband.
I trust you'll permit me to
wait upon you tomorrow.
And to express to you
the depth of my gratitude.
It wasn't...
But it was, my
dear lady. It was.
Will you excuse us?
Excuse me,
but I have to go.
I think Mr. Buchanan
would like a word with you.
Where's our boy?
Where's Hank?
We can talk if
you'll come in here.
So you both knew the time
and the place all along.
Don't be a fool!
An odd coincidence,
both of you turning up here.
Yeah, it's a pity you didn't
contact your assistant.
He told us both
you were here.
I beg your pardon?
We need that help you
offered, Mr. Buchanan.
Sir, we've questioned the
woman. Said she bought a ticket
which happened to
place her in the same box
with the man who
did the shooting.
Didn't know anything. But
if she does, she isn't talking.
I'll see her later.
Very good, sir.
Please tell me everything
now. Everything.
There's still plenty of room
for hope, Mrs. McKenna.
His Excellency
will see you now.
And that's that,
Isuppose.
Yes. All right.
Excuse me, sir. I have
a lot to explain to you.
Something very
unusual has happened.
I also have to have the
money to pay the marksman.
Wouldn't that be superfluous,
considering that he's dead?
His aim wasn't quite as
good as you led me to expect.
The target merely received a
slight flesh wound in the arm.
Worse than useless.
Then your French friend
panicked, made a fatal crash,
landing on the floor
of the Albert Hall.
I don't see how you can
blame me for that, sir.
He was warmly recommended
by our people in Marrakech.
I'm glad that you are able
to treat the matter so lightly.
I'm holding a reception
here this evening.
In a few moments,
I have to welcome
our Prime Minister
as my guest of honor
when I hoped and expected that
he would be totally unable to attend.
That amuses you,
no doubt.
I don't know
what to say.
No.
But I do.
You have muddled
everything from the start.
Taking that child
with you from Marrakech.
Don't you realize that Americans
dislike having their children stolen?
How else could I make sure that
McKenna would keep his mouth shut?
Then to crown it all,
you get cold feet
and come running
along here to hide,
bringing the wretched
child with you.
Don't you see what you've done to
the diplomatic status of this embassy?
I didn't think.
I only thought we could...
How are you going to get
the child out of here?
No difficulty about that,
surely. The car...
With plainclothes detectives
planted right 'round this building?
You English intellectuals
will be the death of us all.
I'll think of something.
Only give me time.
Time.
I want the child removed from this
embassy and removed in such a way
that he won't be able to say
anymore where he has been tonight.
No!
I'll see to it.
Drayton! I trust that nothing
will go wrong this time.
It would be very
unfortunate for you if...
Yes, come in.
Your Excellency, the princess
should be arriving at any moment.
I recognized him.
He recognized me.
He tried to get away, made
a jump for it. That was all.
Trying to liquidate one
of their own big shots.
I wish they'd stick
to their usual custom
and do it in
their own country.
Yes?
Buchanan speaking.
Right. Thank you.
The Draytons are
at the embassy.
The what?
How do you know?
We have means of
finding out from the inside.
Well, look, if the Draytons
are at the embassy,
then our boy's
there too.
You're probably right,
but we can't do anything.
What do you mean,
you can't do anything?
Every embassy in a foreign
country has extraterritorial rights.
What's that?
As far as we're concerned, this
embassy stands on foreign soil.
So they can steal kids and
get away with it? What is this?
We could have
the Foreign Office
serve a writ on
the Ambassador.
You know, I'm not responsible for
the complications of international law.
If only we had some positive
proof that your boy really is in there.
Say, what's the phone
number of that embassy?
You got it?
What are you
thinking about?
Let me try something.
Grosvenor 0144.
Grosvenor 0144,
please.
That fellow that got shot's
a prime minister, isn't he?
Hello? Hello. I'd like to speak
to the Prime Minister, please.
Yeah, yeah. No, look.
Just tell him the lady that saved
his life would like to speak to him.
It's very important.
Yeah.
Ben, what do I say?
He wanted to visit with
us so he could thank you.
Tell him you want to come over
to the embassy right away, tonight,
'cause we're going to leave
London tomorrow. You see?
Hello? Here you are.
Hello?
My dear lady, this is
a charming surprise.
Delighted.
Delighted, delighted.
The Ambassador too
would be delighted.
Any friends of mine
are friends of his.
He said all right.
So if he asks you,
we're all set. You see?
But supposing
they don't?
Honey, have we ever been to a
party where they didn't ask you?
Now, your job is to
hold their attention, right?
Good evening.
It's Dr. and Mrs. McKenna.
How very nice
to see you.
The Prime Minister's
waiting for you.
Do come this way,
please.
Madame.
Good evening,
good evening.
Good evening.
This is the charming lady who
saved my life at the concert.
Madam, you saved
the life of the one man
who's irreplaceable
in our country.
I hear you are the famous
Jo Conway, madame.
Yes, I'm Jo Conway.
Perhaps we might...
I'm sure my wife would
be delighted to sing for you.
Wouldn't you, dear?
Well, it's been
quite some time.
I beg you, madame.
A tranquil coda
to conclude
a dramatic evening.
I'm very flattered.
Stanis? Would you put up
some chairs? And hurry up, please.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the famous Jo Conway
has gladly consented
to sing a few songs
for us tonight.
Darling, would you see that the
Prime Minister gets a very good seat?
Would you like to
come to the piano?
Would you not like
to sit down, sir?
No, thank you. I'll
just stand over here.
When
I was just a little girl
I asked my mother
what will I be
Win 1 be pretty?
Will I be rich?
Here's what she said to me
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
When I was just
a child in school
I asked my teacher
what should I try
Should I paint pictures?
Should I sing songs?
This was her wise reply
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
When I grew up
and fell in love
I asked my sweetheart
what lies ahead
Will we have rainbows
day after day?
Here's what my sweetheart said
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
That's my mother's voice!
That's my mother singing!
What?
Are you sure, Hank?
Are you quite sure?
That's her! I know it!
What's she doing here?
Hank, can you
whistle that song?
I guess so.
Then go on.
Whistle it.
Whistle it
as loud as you can.
Will we have rainbows
day after day?
Here's what my sweetheart said
Ever Will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
Now I have children of my own
They ask their mother
what will I be
Win 1 be handsome?
Will I be rich?
I tell them tenderly
Que sera, sera
Whatever will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
What will be, will be
You two wait in the mail
room. I'll bring him down.
Give me about
five minutes.
No!
Daddy!
Take the boy. Go! But be
quick. You must be quick!
Come on, son.
Go on!
Just a moment,
please.
Don't touch him.
I don't think you're gonna
do any shooting, Drayton,
not with these people
downstairs and the police outside.
You're not in a very happy
position yourself, you know.
You've got to
let the boy go!
Precisely what I'm
thinking, my dear.
Now I'm sure you're going to be
sensible and help me out of here.
Don't ask me for help,
you miserable...
You wouldn't want your father
to get hurt, would you, Hank?
Now we're going to
walk downstairs together
quite casually like
three old friends.
Then we're going to
take a little stroll
as far as the
nearest taxi rank.
And I hope there won't be any
emotional scenes on the way down.
Do as he says, Hank.
No, the other way.
Shall we be going?
All right, start
down the hall, son.
Don't say anything.
Now it's good-bye
And we're facing
such lonely tomorrows
So many sunsets
Till there's a sunset
When all at once,
you'll be there
Then we'll kiss again
And again
Come on, Hank.
Mother!
I'm sorry we
were gone so long,
but we had to go over
and pick up Hank.