I didn't sleep well last night, and
I woke up with a scratchy throat.
I just don't feel so
good. Uh, cough.
Yeah, um-um, I have a bit of an
upset stomach too, and I
think I'm running a fever.
I'm just worried I
might be contagious.
Inventory. Tomorrow. I'm—Yeah,
I'm sure I'll be feeling better by then.
Thanks, Mr. Innabe.
I cannot believe
you just did that.
I-I really do have a cough.
Oh. So you weren't lying.
You'd be curled up in bed
with a bowl of chicken soup...
Even if you didn't have
a horny girl in your bed?
Yes. Because I really do— Hey.
I really do have a cough.
You also have a little rash.
Um, I'm not sure
we should be kissing.
Oh. It's okay. Because I have
almost no interest in kissing you.
Perfect. Good.
Uh-uh-uh.
Oh, baby.
Oh, Brandon.
Brandon.
I know I'm good, but come on.
Brandon?
Brandon. Brandon. Brandon.
Brandon! Brandon!
Any additional R. N. to Surgical.
Why do you want
me to treat this guy?
Blood pressure's not
responding to I.V. fluids.
No, no. I didn't ask how you
plan to con me into treating him.
I asked you why you
want me to treat him.
He's sick. I care. I'm pathetic.
There are about a billion sick
people on the planet. Why this one?
Because this one's in our emergency
room. Ah, so it's a proximity issue.
If somebody was
sick in the third-floor
stairwell, that's who'd
we be talking about.
Yes. I checked the
stairwell. It's clear.
Okay, then. Emergency
room guy it is.
Wait. Why was that so
easy? You know why.
- Blood pressure's not responding to
I.V. fluids?
- Yeah.
That's just weird.
C.B.C. was unremarkable. Abdominal
C.T. scan didn't show anything.
So, people, differential
diagnosis. What's wrong with her?
- Him.
- Him. Her. Does it matter?
Does anyone think it's a
testicular problem? No. So, Chase?
- Yersinia infection?
- No. You wouldn't get the rash or cough.
What about arthritis? Accompanying
vasculitis causes nerve damage...
- No. It wouldn't cause
the blood pressure problems. Allergy?
- The kid's got abdominal pain.
Maybe carcinoid? No. But
then you wouldn't get the...
Foreman, if you're going
to list all the things it's
not, it might be quicker
to do it alphabetically.
Let's see, now. "Absidia." Excellent.
Doesn't account for any of the symptoms.
- No condition accounts for
all these symptoms.
- Oh, good.
Because I thought maybe he
was sick. But, apparently, he's not.
Who wants to do up
the discharge papers?
Okay. Unless we control
the blood pressure,
he's gonna start circling the drain before
we can figure out what's wrong with him.
Treat him for sepsis,
broad-spectrum antibiotics,
and I want a Cort-stim
test and an echocardiogram.
You all right? Yeah.
The Cort-stim test will
tell us if your pituitary
and adrenal glands
are working properly.
- His glands? What does that mean?
- We have a few theories we're working on.
- You mean you don't know.
- Mindy.
I'm just saying, if they knew they wouldn't
be testing you, they'd be treating you.
Yeah, well, that's the
way it works. First we
find out what it is,
then we get you better.
You're half an hour
late. Busy caseload.
One case is not a load.
So how are we doing
on cotton swabs today? If
there's an acute shortage,
I could run home...
No, you couldn't. Nice.
Hello, sick people
and their loved ones.
In the interest of saving
time and avoiding a lot
of boring chitchat later,
I'm Dr. Gregory House.
You can call me Greg. I'm one of three
doctors staffing this clinic this morning.
Short. Sweet. Grab a file. This
ray of sunshine is Dr. Lisa Cuddy.
Dr. Cuddy runs this
whole hospital, so,
unfortunately, she's much
too busy to deal with you.
I am a board-certified
diagnostician,
with a double specialty of
infectious disease and nephrology.
I'm also the only doctor
currently employed at this
clinic who is forced to
be here against his will.
That is true, isn't
it? But not to worry.
Because for most of you, this job could be
done by a monkey with a bottle of Motrin.
Speaking of which, if you’re particularly
annoying, you may see me reach for this.
This is Vicodin. It's
mine. You can't have any.
And, no, I do not have a pain
management problem. I have a pain problem.
But who knows? Maybe I'm
wrong. Maybe I'm too stoned to tell.
So, who wants me?
And who would rather wait
for one of the other two guys?
Okay. Well, I'll be in Exam Room
One if you change your mind.
Jodi Matthews?
Please accompany
Dr. House to Exam Room One.
Dr. Chase.
I'm not sure scaring your boyfriend
is the best medicine for him right now.
I know. I get stupid when I'm
scared. Don't go rock climbing.
Look, I was wondering. Before
this happened, we were having sex.
What? You're wondering if whatever
he has, you might've gotten it?
It-It's unlikely. We ran a
complete S.T.D. panel, so...
No. I'm wondering if maybe I
did this to him. I was kind of rough.
It was yellow. It was?
It's not anymore.
Well, that's a shame.
I thought that might be a
problem, so I brought you this.
Your mucus was "pale goldenrod."
Last week, yes. Should I
be worried? Oh, yes. Very.
Really? I thought
it was okay now.
And yet, here you
are. What happened?
Paramedics took a week
to respond to your 911 call?
You're not a very
nice doctor, are you?
And you are very bad
at whatever it is you do.
You don't even know me. I
know you're gonna get fired.
That's why you got the new glasses.
That's why your teeth are sparkly white.
You're getting the most of your
health insurance while you still can.
I might be quitting.
If you were quitting, you'd
have known that last week when
your snot was still pale
goldenrod. You're getting fired.
I just don't like
being told what to do.
I can get you in for a full
body scan later this week.
Thanks.
It's got to be viral. We should
start running gels and titers.
Maybe we should look into the girlfriend's
theory. She thinks she rode him to death.
What'd you tell her?
I told her 22-year-old
men don't die of sex.
- What'd you ask her?
- What do you mean?
I mean, I hope you got some
specifics on exactly what was going on.
If the girl thinks it could kill
you, it's worth knowing about.
Have you ever taken a life?
We should stop the antibiotics.
It's too soon to say
they're not having an effect.
They're having an effect.
His B. P. 's falling fast.
There's fluid filling his lungs.
His creatinine is rising.
His kidneys are shutting down.
Our treatment isn't making
him better. It's killing him.
So, we had six symptoms
that didn't add up
to anything. Now we
got seven. Who's excited?
I don't think it
complicates things. The
kidney failure was
caused by the antibiotics.
- Maybe.
- Typically, low blood pressure
and abdominal pain means an infection.
An abdominal infection causes
sepsis, low blood pressure.
Except we checked
for abdominal infections.
But what if it's the other
way around? What if the
low blood pressure's
causing the abdominal pain?
Viral heart infection.
The intestines aren't
getting enough blood,
and the result is belly pain.
- I know it's not
the standard presentation.
- It's a 10 million-to-1 shot.
I thought that's what
we dealt with here.
It explains the cardiomyopathy,
the pain, the low B.P., the fever.
You read the book. Impressive.
It's a ludicrously long
shot that explains every one
of those symptoms— except
for the cough and the rash.
Should we just erase those?
Well, anything can cause a rash.
Okay. Cardiac infection.