I didn't sleep well last night, and
I woke up with a scratchy throat.
I just don't feel so
good. Uh, cough.
Yeah, um-um, I have a bit of an
upset stomach too, and I
think I'm running a fever.
I'm just worried I
might be contagious.
Inventory. Tomorrow. I'm—Yeah,
I'm sure I'll be feeling better by then.
Thanks, Mr. Innabe.
I cannot believe
you just did that.
I-I really do have a cough.
Oh. So you weren't lying.
You'd be curled up in bed
with a bowl of chicken soup...
Even if you didn't have
a horny girl in your bed?
Yes. Because I really do— Hey.
I really do have a cough.
You also have a little rash.
Um, I'm not sure
we should be kissing.
Oh. It's okay. Because I have
almost no interest in kissing you.